Whoa, that was a tough concept, but you handled it really well.
哇，剛才那個概念還真不是那麼好理解的， 但你做得不錯
This unlocks the ability to build some really awesome layouts in Android
這將解開讓你在 Android 裏頭創造 相當漂亮的佈局的能力，
because almost all screens contain some type of nested layouts,
因爲幾乎所有的屏幕 都有某種嵌套佈局
which Correll was actually mentioning earlier in the Google Play app.
這個 Correll 剛在 Google Play 應用程式那邊就有提及
After all of that prep work, now we're ready to go back into
準備工作完成後， 現在我們終於可以
Android Studio land to implement the changes for an improved quantity picker.
回到 Android Studio 那邊去 實施改變打造一個更好的數量選擇器
In case you're wondering, Katherine, what if I'm trying to build a layout and
對了，凱薩琳，如果你正在想 要是我想打造一個佈局，
I don't have three options of XML layouts
但我卻沒有 三項 XML 佈局選項
magically appear before me that I have to choose from.
很奇蹟的出現在我面前讓我選擇， 那我該怎麼辦呢？
Well, that's a fair question.
這是很好的問題
So far we've practiced being able to read XML and
到目前爲止，我們已經練習過 怎麼閱覽 XML
draw a view hierarchy diagram.
和怎麼畫視圖的層次圖
We've also practiced reading XML layouts and
我們也已經練習過 怎麼閱覽 XML 佈局
drawing a sketch of what the screen would look like.
和畫過屏幕裏面看起來 會是什麼樣子的草圖
But now it's time to practice seeing a design of what we want to build and
那麼，現在是時候練習 怎麼看到我們想要打造的設計
being able to write the XML from it.
和怎麼編寫這個設計的 XML 了
I do realize that I gave you the solution XML in the previous quiz.
在之前的測驗裏頭，我清楚記得 已經給你提供所需的 XML 解決方案
I was somewhat paying attention, but I don't want you to look at that solution.
我是有注意到沒錯， 但我不想你現在去看那份解決方案
I want you to practice the skill of seeing a screenshot or
我想要你練習 看着一個屏幕截圖，
a mock of what you want to build and then being able to write the XML for it.
或是一份你想打造的東西的模擬， 然後編寫出它的 XML 來
Normally, we would start with the desired screenshot
一般來說，我們會先從 我們想要打造的東西
of what we want to build.
的屏幕截圖開始
You can get this from a designer that's working on your team who's
你可以從你的團隊裏頭， 那個正在給你設計應用程式的
designing the app for you.
設計師哪兒獲得
Or if you're working without a designer,
如果你團隊裏頭沒有設計師，
you could also sketch this out on your own.
你也可以試試看 自己畫一份草圖出來
Then you would imagine how to break this down into views and ViewGroups.
然後你改想象 怎麼將這圖分解成視圖和視圖組
You can mark it up and then try to draw out the view hierarchy diagram for
你可以把它們標籤起來， 然後試着畫出
the relationship between the children and the parent views.
一份它們之間的 父視圖和子視圖關係的層次圖
After you finish this diagram, you can start writing out the skeleton for
當你完成了這份層次圖後， 你就可以開始編寫
what the XML layout code would look like.
你的那份 XML 佈局 看起來會是什麼樣子的一份骨架
I'll leave these parts as an exercise for you.
這些部分 讓你自己來練習
You'll make your changes in the activity_main.xml layout file.
你將會在activity_main.xml 佈局文件裏面 作出你想看到的修改
Aside from writing your XML here and
除了在這裏編寫 XML
seeing a preview of it, you can also click on the design pane here.
和觀看預覽以外， 你也可以點擊這個設計面板
This is Design tab as opposed to the Text tab.
這是和文本標籤不同的 設計標籤
The Design pane allows you to drag and drop views onto the device.
這設計面板讓你將視圖 拖放到設備上去
You can also see the component tree in the top right corner here.
你也可以再右上角 看到組件樹
This is, essentially, a tree of all the views in your hierarchy.
這基本上就是你的所有視圖的層次 形成的組件樹
Currently we have vertical LinearLayout, that's the parent view, and
我們現在有的垂直的LinearLayout 就是父視圖，
all these children views inside of it.
而這些在裏面的就是子視圖
If you had nested ViewGroups, they would also show up here.
如果你有嵌套的 ViewGroup ， 他們也會在這裏顯示出來
Now go ahead and build this layout in Android Studio.
現在就試試怎麼在 Android Studio 打造這個佈局吧
After you've selected and positioned the views, remember to style them so
在你選定和放置視圖以後， 記得要這麼放，
it looks like this.
才會看起來像這樣
The style of the views is mostly the same,
視圖的風格 大致上都是一樣的，
except note that there's eight dp of space in-between the minus button and
但要注意的是， 減按鈕和二之間，
the two and in-between the two and the plus button.
或二和加按鈕之間， 有 8 dp 的空間
As mentioned earlier, avoid looking at the code and
如早前說過的一樣， 試着不要看編碼，
try implementing it yourself.
而是靠你自己實踐出來
When you're done, check this box to continue.
完成以後， 請確認這個框繼續